<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to Follow My Stomach on Follow My Stomach</title>
    <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to Follow My Stomach on Follow My Stomach</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:22:50 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dev.followmystomach.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Ready to Go</title>
      <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 11:05:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>This page is about preparing for your trip abroad, specifically focusing on the cooking and food experience you want to have when traveling.
Research and Motivation You don&amp;rsquo;t have to research before you leave but it can be helpful and motivating.
If you like to read about food culture, books can be useful during long flights/transportation. For example, &amp;hellip;links to food books.
Use your tv/netflix/etc viewing habits to help motivate you and give you ideas about what to eat and where to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Do Upon Arrival</title>
      <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/arrival/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 13:31:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/arrival/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m presuming here that you&amp;rsquo;ve already rested from the flight/trip if it&amp;rsquo;s necessary. Duh.
Assess the Apartment Situation Check out your kitchen space and the provided tools. Here are some questions to consider:
What size is the fridge? This has rarely been a problem for me but if the fridge is very small, you need to consider this when buying items that need refridgeration.
How many burners does the stove have (presuming there is one)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groceries</title>
      <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/groceries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 13:31:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/groceries/</guid>
      <description>This page is about shopping for groceries when traveling, specifically using grocery stores and super markets as opposed to street/farmers&amp;rsquo; markets.
Grocery Store Tips  Visit several to see what they offer Learn/note their hours Use them to break bigger bills (sparingly) Bring your own bag(s), not everywhere provides them Get your cheap stuff here  Add some stories
Add a list of what I normally buy here
Other Food Shops  Check the prepared foods, some can be amazing Look for friendly merchants and ask them advice and suggestions (people love to give advice) If you find a good proprietor, let them guide you, especially after you&amp;rsquo;ve vetted the place and determined they aren&amp;rsquo;t just trying to take your money  Specialty Foods You could also call these focused food shops: shops specializing in a single thing like meat, fish, cheese, bread, pastries, wine, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markets</title>
      <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 13:31:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/markets/</guid>
      <description>This page is about exploring and taking advantage of foreign markets, specifically the daily or weekly markets that take over a plaza or a parking lot and offer the most variety of fresh ingredients you are likely to find.
 Learn the schedules (many markets are not daily) Can be super cheap Get what&amp;rsquo;s in season Food usually the freshest Get what you know to taste how it differs Explore exotic or unknown ingredients, get stuff you cannot get at home Learn by watching locals shop Get suggestions on recipes/preparation tips Ask for tastes/Don&amp;rsquo;t be shy but don&amp;rsquo;t be an ass Buy small so you don&amp;rsquo;t have waste/leftovers  Next Read about improvising in limited kitchens in the next page in this series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improvising in a Foreign Kitchen</title>
      <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/improvising/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 13:31:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/improvising/</guid>
      <description>Have the right mindset (constraints are good) Save food containers for leftovers Bottle as rolling pin Know when not to improvise, don&amp;rsquo;t force things  Working in a temporary kitchen can be fun but it&amp;rsquo;s often a bit of work and requires some thinking when you plan recipes and buy ingredients. It&amp;rsquo;s very likely you will not have access to a fully-stocked kitchen. How a kitchen is stocked can be a great limiter on what you can cook since it&amp;rsquo;s possible you won&amp;rsquo;t have an oven or may have only one stove burner or will have a very small refrigerator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Recipes</title>
      <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/standard-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 13:31:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.followmystomach.com/travel/guide/standard-recipes/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re going to be traveling for a longer period, it&amp;rsquo;s useful to have a list of core recipes you can use in travel kitchens. These recipes should me these criteria:
 relatively easy to cook you enjoy cooking and eating them easy to find ingredients for don&amp;rsquo;t require special kitchen equipment you&amp;rsquo;re unlikely to have when traveling  A lot of times I find these recipes are also comfort food for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meal Plan For: 2020-04-12</title>
      <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/meal-plans/by-date/2020-04-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 10:39:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.followmystomach.com/meal-plans/by-date/2020-04-12/</guid>
      <description>Before The Week I went to the grocery store last Thursday so the fridge is pretty full. As we had a roasted chicken last week, we now have about a half-gallon of chicken broth I made on Saturday. Bought two chickens so still have one for a few meals this week plus additional broth to make.
During the Week Sunday: Made breadsticks with the standard recipe (yeast, flour, water salt) and I added some paprika to the dough which gave it some fun, streaky coloration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Follow My Stomach</title>
      <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 12:47:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.followmystomach.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This is the about page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparation: Getting Ready to Cook</title>
      <link>http://dev.followmystomach.com/skills/preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:22:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.followmystomach.com/skills/preparation/</guid>
      <description>These tips are primarly for people who have just started cooking or are looking to solidify their foundation of cooking skills. If you&amp;rsquo;re confident in your cooking skills, presumably you&amp;rsquo;ve already established the practices below.
Prepare Properly For so many processes, when you start solidly you are more likely to finish well. Before you start cooking, make sure:
 you have sufficient time you have what you need your working area is clean your ingredients are collected, cleaned and prepared (mise en place)  You Have Sufficient Time This requirement is easy to ignore but luckily easy to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>